How to Meditate, Bombay 29 May 1976.
如何入静,孟买,1976年5月29日
I told you at Dadar, how in Sahaja Yoga, you first go into the state of Tadatmya(oneness with the Divine).
在达卡,我告诉过你们,在霎哈嘉瑜伽是怎样的 首先你进入到Tadatmya的状态(与神合一)
After the Tadatmya  one can attain the stage of Samipya(Nearness to God) and then Salokya(Companionship with God).
在Tadatmya后,可以达到Samipya阶段(与神接近) 之后是Salokya阶段(与神同在)
But on achieving Tadatmya,
但是在达到Tadatmya(与神合一)时
a person’s interest itself changes.
人的兴趣本身发生改变
Immediately on achieving the state of Tadatmya, due to his experiences,
一旦达到Tadatmya(与神合一)阶段,由于他的经验
a person does not wish to go down into the state of Salokya and Samipya.
他不会想要再下降至Salokya(与神同在)和 Samipya(与神接近)的状态
That means, when vibrations start flowing into your hands
就是说,当能量开始在你的双手流动时
and when you feel other’s Kundalini
当你感受到
and can raise their Kundalini,
并提升他人的灵量时
then your chitta (attention)
你的注意力
goes towards watching other’s Kundalini
放在关注他人的灵量
and understanding your own.
以及了解自己的灵量
You want to be alert about your chakras and understand other’s chakras.
你想对自己的轮穴警觉,也理解别人的轮穴
If you look up towards the sky, you may see – even if there are clouds
如果你看向天空,你可能看到,即使有云
you will see many types of Kundalini.
你还是会看到各种形态的灵量
Because, now  your attention has gone to Kundalini,
因为,现在你的注意力已经放在了灵量
whatever you want to know about Kundalini, whatever you want to see,
不管你想了解灵量什么,不管你想看到什么
whatever desires you have,
不管你有什么愿望
these will be revealed to you.
都会在你面前呈现
Your interest in Kundalini grows
你对灵量的兴趣在增长
and all other interests disappear by themselves.
所有其他兴趣都自行消失了
Try to understand thus : As you enter into adulthood, leaving behind the childhood,
试着这样理解:当你步入成年 童年离你而去
you have the interests of your adult life - your job, business, wife, family;
你只对成年的生活感兴趣,工作 生意,妻子,家庭
you take interest only in these and all other childhood interests drop off,
你只对这些感兴趣,其他童年的兴趣逐渐减退
old experiences fade away and your attention goes towards new experiences.
旧的体验逐渐消失,你的注意力转向新的体验
Or try to understand this way: Say, a person is not interested in music,
或者尝试这样理解:比如说 有个人对音乐不感兴趣
and somehow he has become interested in music, in classical music,
不知怎地他对音乐感兴趣了 对古典音乐感兴趣
then he is not going to enjoy
之后他就不会再享受
any other non-classical music concert.
非古典音乐会
Your condition in Sahaja Yoga should also be similar.
你在霎哈嘉瑜伽就类似这样
As regards your other habits and interests,
至于你的其他习惯和兴趣
they are acquired gradually and intentionally cultivated
它们是被逐渐习得和有意熏陶的
and hence those interests are deeply imbibed in you.
因此这些兴趣深深地渗透在你内里
Sahaja Yoga has brought about a complete transformation in you,
霎哈嘉瑜伽在你的内在带来全然的转化
– you have come into a state of new awareness,
你已经进入到一个新的知觉
you can now feel the vibrations and other’s Kundalini,
现在你可以感受到能量和他人的灵量
you can give realization to many people, you have cured thousands of people,
你可以给很多人自觉 你可以治疗成千上万的人
you have entered into a new power
你已经进入到一个新的力量之中
and you are nourished by it.
并被这个力量滋养着
But in doing all this there is only one shortcoming,
但在做这一切时有一个唯一的缺点
and that is that you have not made any effort and everything has happened by itself, effortlessly.
就是你丝毫没有费力,一切都是 自己发生的,毫不费力
Perhaps that’s the reason why, although
也许这就是为何
many people receive vibrations in Sahaja Yoga and also rise to a very high state,
尽管很多人在霎哈嘉瑜伽中获得了能量 也升进到很高的状态
even then their attention
但接下来他们的注意力
never stabilizes on Paramatma, Atma, or Kundalini
却从来没有稳定在Paramatma(至高的灵) 真我,或者灵量上
and it  repeatedly goes towards wrong things.
而是反复地走向错误的事情
You had asked me, “What is to be done after getting realization”.
你们已经问过我,“获得自觉后要做什么“
After receiving (realisation)you have to give.
获得自觉后你必须要给予
It is absolutely necessary to give after receiving your realisation, otherwise receiving (it) has no meaning.
在获得自觉后去给予是绝对有必要的 否则获得自觉没有意义
And while giving, one point – only one small point, must be kept in mind,
当给予时,有一点,一小点,必须要谨记
“That with this body, this mind (manas), this intellect (buddhi),—that means the ‘whole personality’
“就是藉由这个身体,这个思维(manas) 这个智性,也就是说'整个人格‘
with which you are giving such an incomparable thing, that itself should be very beautiful;
藉由它你给予无与伦比的事物(自觉) 它自身要非常的美丽
your being should be very clean.”
你的存有要非常的洁净”
Before coming to Sahaja Yoga you must be getting worried and wishing that the disease should be somehow cured.
在来到霎哈嘉瑜伽之前,你可能会很担心 疾病,并希望疾病以某种方式被治愈
But thereafter the attention does not go onto your sickness and you start saying, “It will be alright, does not matter.”
来到霎哈嘉后,你的注意力不再放在疾病上 你开始说,“病会好的,没关系”
But it is wrong Whatever may be your problem, even minor,
但这是错误的,不管你有什么问题 即使是很小的问题
you can cure yourself by placing your hand on that spot, you can keep your physical side very clean.
你也能治疗自己,通过把手放在那个地方 你能保持身体层面的洁净
There is not much to be done. Just meditate and keep yourself clean, keep your physical side clean.
没太多需要做的.只是静坐,保持自己的洁净 保持身体方面的洁净
However, for you I have told you one important thing.
但是,我已经告诉你们一件重要的事情
As it is said, everyone must go to bathroom and clean oneself after getting up in the morning.
就像(在印度)每个人早晨起床后 必须去浴室洁净自己
. Similarly, for Sahaja Yogis, it is extremely important to do foot-soaking for at least five minutes, before going to bed.
同样的,对霎哈嘉瑜伽士来说,入睡前 做至少五分钟的足浴是极为重要的
However highly evolved you may be and even if you may not be getting caught – but it does not matter.
不管你进化得多高,即使你没有被感染 这没关系
You must do foot-soaking for at least five minutes. Even I do foot-soaking sometimes,
你必须要泡脚,至少五分钟.甚至连我有时 都要泡脚(尽管我是没必要泡脚的)
(although it is not necessary for me) so that my Sahaja Yogis will imbibe this habit. It is a very good habit.
好使我的霎哈嘉瑜伽士 吸收这个习惯,这是非常好的习惯
All Sahaja Yogis must do foot-soaking for at least for five minutes,daily. All Sahaja Yogis,
所有霎哈嘉瑜伽士必须每天泡脚,至少五分钟 每天都要做.所有的霎哈嘉瑜伽士
should light a deep(lamp) before the photograph,
要在照片前点上油灯
apply sindur (vermilion), dip their feet in water
点上红色吉祥痣,将双足放进水中
and sit in this fashion opening out both the palms towards the photograph.
双手摊开朝向照片坐好
If you do this, more than half of your problems would be solved automatically.
如果你这么做,一半以上的问题会自动解决
Whatever happens, it is not difficult to spare five minutes.
无论发生什么事,挤出五分钟并不困难
All should sit like this before going to sleep.
每个人都应该在睡前这么坐着
That will stop more than half of your catches.
它能去除半数以上的感染
We must get up early in the morning.
我们必须早起
Our sahaja yoga is a day time activity, not of night.
我们的霎哈嘉瑜伽是日间活动,不是夜间的
So one must sleep early at night.
因此人们晚上必须早睡
I am not asking you to sleep at 6 pm but by 10 pm all must go to sleep.
我不是要你们在六点就睡,但所有人都该 在十点前去睡觉
You should not stay awake after 10. You must get up early in the morning.
你们不该在十点后还醒着 你们必须在清晨起床
In the morning after getting up early & taking your bath, one must sit for meditation.
清晨早起后,沐浴一下,就必须坐下来静坐
In the morning one must sit for meditation.
清晨必须坐下来静坐
Like, in our country, we have been getting up early in the morning
像在我们国家,自古以来我们会早起沐浴
and washing up our selves since ages and have been doing it all our lives.
一辈子都是这样
In the same way all sahaja yogis must get up early and meditate in the morning.
同样的,所有霎哈嘉瑜伽士必须 在清晨早起静坐
It is a question forming a habit.
这是习惯养成的问题
But I have seen that for many it is very difficult to get up early at 4am or 5am.
但我发现对许多人来说,清晨四点或五点 起床是十分困难的
There is reason for that. I have done in-depth study about human beings. It is very joyful to study them.
这是有原因的,我对人类做了彻底的研究 研究他们是很愉悦的
It is very interesting to see how human beings runs way from himself and argues against himself.
看着人们如何自我逃避、自我争辩是 十分有趣的
It is quite interesting to see how he gives explanation about himself and makes himself an object of mockery.
看着他们如何给自己辩解、把自己变成 受嘲笑的对象,也充满乐趣
Some people tell me, Mother we cannot get u early in the morning.
有些人对我说:"母亲我们无法早起"
I say when did you go to sleep last night. 12 ‘O clock. But I had decided Mother, that I shall get up at 4 ‘O clock.
我问他们昨晚几点睡觉. "十二点,但母亲 我决定我应该要四点起床"
That is impossible. But you must sleep early one day and must get up early next morning.
这是不可能的,你们前一天应该要早睡 然后第二天早起
Then you shall fall asleep early that day.
接着你们当天应该要早点睡
You do that for 2 or 3 days and your body shall get accustomed to it.
持续两三天好让身体习惯
When you get up early in the morning, your receptivity is more.
当你们早起,接收能力也会更强
Not only that, at that early hour in the world also extremely beautiful (vibrations?)
不只如此,世界刚开始的时辰是极其美好的 (讲话因麦克风问题而中断)
So from the point of view of body I have told you and also that one must meditate in the morning.
所以我已经解释了,从身体的角度来看 人们也该在早晨静坐
Now how to meditate. Think about it, how to meditate early in the morning.
那么如何静坐呢?试想一下 清晨该如何静坐
First bow down yourself in your heart. Humble down yourself.
首先在心里顺从,让自己谦卑下来
If someone thinks that he has achieved a lot or „I am a very big saint”,
如果有人认为自己已经有很多成就 或者"我是个非常伟大的圣人"
then take it for granted that he is a gone case. He is about to go out of sahaja yoga.
那理所当然地他是个要离开的例子 他快离开霎哈嘉瑜伽了
One should take permission and sit peacefully before the photograph with palms spread out
一个人应当请求允许,在照片前平静地坐下来 双手摊开
and with extreme humbleness one must bow towards one’s heart.
必须怀有极度的谦卑向内心顺服
One has to ask for forgiveness repeatedly.
要反复地请求宽恕
So even at that time one must ask for forgiveness that
即便是那时人们也要请求宽恕
„O God if have committed any mistake against yourself, please forgive us and take us into meditation".
“噢!主啊!如果我们犯下任何违反祢的过错 请宽恕我们,将我们带入静坐中”
Then we pray, we forgive all those who have done any harm to us and if we had harmed anyone
然后我们祈祷:我们宽恕所有伤害过我们的人 如果我们伤害过他人
then please forgive us ‘O Lord. At this point bring pure emotions in your heart and then go into meditation. Now meditate with your eyes closed.
也请宽恕我们,噢!主啊!此时此刻将纯洁的情绪 带入心中,然后入静.现在闭上眼入静
Now one should not ask for how many minutes.
不要问要花多少时间
It is very wrong to ask such questions.
问这样的问题是非常错误的
Whether you meditate for 5 minutes or 10 minutes. For five or ten minutes one must meditate with complete oneness of attention.
无论是静坐五或十分钟,这五或十分钟 必须有完全合一的注意力
umbly bow down yourself and meditate. But before meditation, one must understand it very carefully,
谦卑下来去入静.但在入静前 你们必须非常小心地去理解
before meditating give bandhan to the place where you are going to sit for meditation.
在静坐前必须要对静坐的地方划班单
Give yourself a bandhan,
给自己一个班单
give your body a bandhan, 7 times give your body a bandhan,
给自己的身体班单,给身体划七次
give that place a bandhan, give bandhan to photograph.
给场地划班单,对照片划班单
This is not be done in a mechanical way like many people do
这不是像许多人一样机械化地去做
but with humility and shraddha one must give bandhan as if one is doing a puja.
而是要带着谦卑与坚信(Shraddha)去划班单 就好像去做普祭一样
Do not do exactly like a Puja: ofering, etc.
(不需要献祭等做普祭的流程)
After that give your ‘Mana’ a bandhan.
在那之后给你的'Mana'班单
Now where is ‘Mana’.
"Mana"在哪呢？
You have never asked me, Mother where is ‘mana’.
你们从未问过我"母亲,Mana在那儿?"
Mana is here. It starts from here. Meaning you must give forceful bandhan to vishuddhi and agnya chakra. Mana has to be given a bandhan.
"Mana"在这儿,由这里开始.意思是你们必须要对 喉轮与额轮给出有力的班单,要给"Mana"划班单
While giving bandhan one must have this thought that O Lord, let us remain in your bandhan and nothing untoward may happen to us.
在划班单时要这么想着:噢！主啊！请让我们在祢的 班单之下,没有任何麻烦会发生在我们身上
Bow down with extreme humility. At that time, just assume that you are in witness state
怀着极度谦卑叩拜.那时,只是确信你在静观状态
and detached from everything.
和对一切无执着之中
Just make yourself detached from everything and meditate.
只是让自己脱离一切执着,静坐
If you try this daily, it will become a habit.
如果你尝试每天这样做,就会成为一个习惯
With extreme shradhha one must meditate early in the morning,
一个人要带着极大的虔敬,清晨必须静坐
may be for ten minutes or half an hour, it does not matter.
可以静坐十分钟或半小时,都没关系
While meditating do not move your hands.
当静坐时手不要动
Just watch the photograph and slowly close your eyes
看着照片,慢慢闭上眼睛
while meditating and do not move your hands.
手不要动
At that time whichever chakra is having imbalance,
在那时任何轮穴有不平衡
it can be corrected by just watching that chakra
只是静观那轮穴,就可以纠正过来
because as I have said, Divine vibrations are more in the morning.
因为就象我说的,神圣的生命能量 在清晨时是更多的
Now after having purified our chakras,
在清洁我们的轮穴后
meditate on your Atma-tatva.
冥想你们的真我原理
Take your attention to your Atma(Spirit).
把你的注意力放在你的真我(灵体)
Nobody has ever asked me,Mother where is Atma(The Spirit).
从来没有人问过我什么是真我(灵体)
Atma is in our heart but its seat is on our sahasrara.
真我(Atma)位于我们的心,但它的宝座却在顶轮
That is why I had said that bow down to your heart
这便是为何我说向你们的心拜服
and take your attention to your sahasrara and be surrendered to Atma.
并将注意力放在顶轮,向真我顺服
With thought be surrendered towards the spirit. What is the essence of Atma-tatva.
思想上向真我顺服,什么是真我原理 (Atma-tatva)的本质
Atma-tatva is purity.
真我原理是纯洁
One should say, complete Nirmal purity.
我们应该说,完全的纯洁无暇
Take your attention towards that.
将注意力放在那
That is completely detached. It is not attached with anything.
那便是完全的无执着,不执着于任何事物
Due to your identifications(attachments), you are away from your spirit.
由于你们的自我认同(执着) 你们远离了真我
Meditate on Atma-tatva. And this Atma-tatva is Love.
对真我原理冥想,这真我原理即是爱
Meditate on this.
对此冥想
It is very Great – Atma Tatva is Love.
这是非常伟大的,真我原理即是爱
Many religions have established in this world, but nobody has been able to describe Love in any of those religions.
许多宗教在世上建立,但没有人能在这些宗教中 阐述爱.因此这些宗教里面发生了许多荒谬的事情
Love cannot be described but Love is that power that is flowing from your hands.
爱无法被阐述,但爱是由你们双手流出的力量
This is the ‘Chetna’ awareness that people know as awareness.
这便是"Chetna"觉知力,常人所理解的觉知力
But they do not know that this is Love.
但他们并不知道这就是爱
They comprehend awareness as any other power like electricity.
他们将觉知力理解为其他类型的力量,像电力
But no. Atma-tatva is Love.
但不是这样.真我原理是爱
By saying one word, LOVE,
藉由说出"爱"这个字
you are librated from many bandhans(bondages).
你们从许多束缚中解脱出来
Whatever is false, untruth is against Love.
那些假的,反真理的事物与爱相违背
Even if you are scolding someone and telling them about Truth, you are loving him.
你们向别人阐明真理,即便是责骂某人 你们也是爱他的
You yourself have become Love(Prem),
你们自己本身成为爱
that’s why by just meditating on Prem-Tatva
这便是为何只是对爱的原理(Prem-Tatva)冥想
you can get into Atma-tatva.
你们就可以达到真我原理
While meditating do not get stuck into any one thought.
静坐时不要卡在任何思维上
I am that Atma-tatva.
“我是那爱的原理(Prem-Tatva) 我是真我的原理
I am that power of God Almighty.
“我是全能上主的力量"
You can say like that.
你们可以这样说
This way, by just saying 2-3 times you shall feel blessed. Because you are saying the Truth,
这样说两三遍,你们将会感受到祝福 因为你们说的是真理
vibrations start flowing from your being with great force.
能量以强大的力量开始由你们的存有流动
Now what should be done in day to day life.
现在,日常生活中该做什么呢？
In your daily life, you must know
在你的日常生活中,你要明白
that the power within you is of Prem-tatva (Principiul Dragostei).
你们内在的力量是爱的原理
Whatever you do,
无论做什么
are you doing it in love or you are just trying to show off that you are a great sahaja yogi.
你们是为爱而做,还是只是为了炫耀自己 是个伟大的霎哈嘉瑜伽士
If I say something to anybody or if I get angry with someone
如果我对某人说了什么,或者我对某人发怒
then i notice that they he speaks against Me to other sahaja yogis and then he asks me
接着我发现他会对其他霎哈嘉瑜伽士说些 反对我的话,然后才来问我
„why have I lost my vibrations.”
“为什么我失去自己的生命能量了"
If you are indulging in such foolishness then it is better that you leave sahaja yoga.
如果你们沉溺在这种愚蠢中,那么最好离开 霎哈嘉瑜伽
Only those who are desirous of taking something can stay in sahaja yoga.
只有那些愿望得到的人能留在霎哈嘉瑜伽
He has no right to give Me anything, he only has to accept it from Me.
他没有权"给我"任何东西,他只能从我这儿接受
If he wants to give then when his powers are developed
当他的力量建立好时,如果他想要给予
then it would be very good.
这是很好的
But you can give only when you are able to absorb.
但你们只能在能够吸收时才去给予
Therefore first learn to absorb.
因此首先学会吸收
Try to see your shortcomings.
试着去看看自己的弱点
For our benevolence we should see what we want to give.
因我们的仁慈,我们要去看看自己想给予什么
We are giving love.
我们要给予爱
Are we standing in Love?
我们是站在爱的立场吗
We fight with everyone,
我们与每个人抗争
we argue with everyone, we trouble others
与每个人起争执,烦扰别人
and we think we are sahaja yogis.
然后还认为自己是霎哈嘉瑜伽士
We should not live with this falsehood.
我们不该活在这种错误中
We should live with ourselves like a mirror
我们应该活得像面镜子
meaning we should watch ourselves all the time.
也就是说我们要随时观看自己
Like if something is sticking on to my face and you inform me about that
就像我脸上沾了东西,你们提醒我
and I can wipe it.
然后我将之挥去一样
In the same way you should watch yourself
同样地你们应该观看自己
and wipe off anything that is sticking to you.
并将沾附在你们身上的东西挥除
In your day to day life, you should live a brighter life.
在你们日常生活中,应该过着更灿烂的生活
There should be transformation in your face.
面容应该有转变
Your behaviour has to be beautiful. Love should flow from you. If you are an individual without love
你们的举止应当美好,爱应该由你们之中 流淌而出.如果你们是缺乏爱的个体
then you are not a sahaja yogi.
那么便不是个霎哈嘉瑜伽士
You should know this.
你们应该明白这一点
You have become a sahaja yogi without any desire for it and without proving your worth and I am tolerating you and you are sitting here today.
你们没有任何愿望,也没有证明自己值得 就成为了霎哈嘉瑜伽士,而我忍受了 你们今天坐在了这里
If you cannot improve then please forgive me and stop coming to sahaja yoga.
如果你们无法改进,那么请原谅, 不要来霎哈嘉瑜伽
Such people will themselves go out of sahaja yoga in a few days time.
这样的人几天后会自己离开霎哈嘉瑜伽
şThose who are devoid of love, those who think they are highly evolved, are useless for sahaja yoga.
那些缺乏爱,那些认为自己进化很高的人 对霎哈嘉瑜伽是没用的
Such people should go to other ku-gurus(Fake gurus) and get kicked by them and feel the heat.
这样的人应该去其他假导师那儿 被他们踢几脚、感受热力
Here in sahaja yoga you have come to become instrument of God Almighty.
在霎哈嘉瑜伽你们成为全能上主的工具
You should be extremely humble, extremely humble.
你应该极为谦卑,极为谦卑
You should give up ego completely. Others say one has to take sanyaas(renunciation),
必须完全放弃自我.其他人说必须要过着 苦修(弃绝)的生活
I say first give up your ego. Give up your anger.
我说首先要放弃你的自我,放弃你的愤怒
By taking out your clothes you have not renounced anything.
藉由脱掉衣物你们是无法弃绝任何东西的
Renunciation means giving up anger,lust,attachment,pride greed, jealousy etc.
弃绝是指放弃愤怒、色欲、执着、骄傲、 贪婪、忌妒等
giving up these shadripus(the six enemies) is called sanyaas – sanyast. We are not talking about superficial renunciation.
放弃这六大敌人才称作"弃绝" 我们谈论的不是肤浅的弃绝
You should be extremely loving and peaceful while dealing with others.
当与人相处时你们必须极为有爱、平和
You should be talking about sahaja yoga with your family,children and friends.
你们应该对家人、孩子与朋友谈论霎哈嘉瑜伽
Change your friends and acquaintances.
换掉你们的朋友与熟人
They(sahaja yogis) are your real relations.
他们(霎哈嘉瑜伽士)才是你们真正的亲人
You should talk to them. They(sahaja yogis) will tell you that we have entered into a new world,
你们应该跟他们交谈.他们(霎哈嘉瑜伽士) 会告诉你们:我们进入了新的世界
we have new vibratory awareness.
拥有新的能量的觉知力
Whenever you travel anywhere ,
当你们四处去旅行时
like someone was telling me he has come from Rahuri,
像有人跟我说过,他从Rahuri来
that just as we carry our personal items while travelling, we also carry ‘teertha’,
当旅行时会带着私人物品,还会同时带着 "teertha"
the water vibrated by my feet is called ‘teertha’, and other vibrated items like kum kum etc.
由我双足发放过能量的水称为"teertha" 还有其他发放过能量的物品,像红粉等
If we find any sick person on the way, we give him ‘teertha’ to drink.
如果路上发现有人生病了,我们会 把"teertha"给他们饮用
If someone talks about religion we show him Mother’s photograph and tell him about Mother
如果有人谈起宗教,我们会向他展示母亲的 照片,告诉他关于母亲的信息
and that she can give you your self realisation.
并告知他母亲可以给予他自觉.路途上不管 遇到谁,他们都与之谈论霎哈嘉瑜伽
They apply kum kum to some and ask them how do they feel,
他们给某些人点上吉祥痣并询问感受
show them my photo and talk about me and tell them that they can get their realisation from this photograph.
向他们展示我的照片、谈论起我,并告诉他们 可以透过照片获得自觉
All the time they only talk of sahaja yoga and only think how they can manifest sahaja yoga.
他们只谈论霎哈嘉瑜伽,也只想着如何 彰显霎哈嘉瑜伽
By doing this you shall find your depth.
藉由这么做你们应当会发现自己的深度
There are also some people who come to sahaja yoga like they visit a temple
也有些人像拜访寺院般而来到霎哈嘉瑜伽
and then they are gone in no time. Due to this they face adverse results.
他们很快就会走掉了,因为这样他们会 面临不好的结果
You will people sitting here, who used to be very sick earlier
你们这群坐在这里的人,有些曾病得很重
but ever since they have received their realisation they have never fallen ill.
但在自觉后他们不再生病
They have never visited a doctor after their realisation.
自觉之后不再看医生
They have never taken any medicine either
也不再吃药
and there are some old people too, who always used to visit doctors, hospitals and have stopped doing so ever since taking to sahaja yoga.
还有些老人原本经常去看医生、进医院 在练习霎哈嘉瑜伽后便停止这么做了
There are many such examples.
有许许多多这样的例子
Not only this but they have also helped others.
不只如此,他们也帮助他人
The reason is that whatever is required to be done as a sahaja yogi for one’s health they kept on doing that and got cured.
原因是,作为一名霎哈嘉瑜伽士, 那些为了维持身体健康需要做的事情, 他们都一直在做,然后获得痊愈
You should all meet each other. Among yourself you are all doctors and all are patients.
你们应该互相见面.你们之间都是医生 也都是病人
Just as doctors do not take fees from one another. In the same way, you also do not take any fees from each other when you help one another.
就像医生不会跟别的医生索取 医药费一样,同样的当帮助彼此时 你们也不对彼此索要金钱
You should treat other and discuss among yourself and you should not mind.
你们应该医治别人,彼此讨论,然后不应该介意
If someone tells you that your sahasrara is caught up then it is a matter of shame
如果有人告诉你你的顶轮感染了 这是比较羞愧的事
because getting at sahasrara means being against Me.
因为顶轮感染意味着反对我
Then you ask others to correct yourself and wonder how you got caught.
你要请其他人修正你,思考一下如何感染的
You should never have anything to do with any person who is against sahaja yoga.
你们不该跟任何反霎哈嘉瑜伽的人有往来
If you do that then your sahasrara is caught up.
如果这么做顶轮就会感染
Do not talk to him and advise him not to talk to you.
你们应该要让这样的人离远一点 闭上眼不去看他
Tell him that you are meeting him due to Mother and that he should keep quite.
告诉他,你们是因为母亲而跟他见面的 他应该要安静点
If you keep talking to such a person
如果你们持续跟这样的人交谈
then your sahasrara is caught up and after a few days you will come to me and say, Mother I have got cancer.
那么顶轮会感染,过没几天你们会跑来 跟我说:"母亲,我得了癌症"
One or two persons had it but now they are cured.
有一两个人曾经是这样的,但现在被治好了
You must know that cancer is a disease of the sahasrara.
你们应当知道癌症是顶轮的疾病
If you have to be free from cancer then keep your sahasrara pure.
如果想摆脱癌症,那么要让顶轮纯净
If your sahasrara starts getting caught up then know that it is the beginning of cancer.
如果顶轮开始感染了,那要知道这是 癌症的开端
You should always keep your sahasrara clean because
你应该一直保持顶轮的洁净
if you do not do so then after a few years you will come and say that you have developed cancer.
因为如果不这么做,几年以后你们会 跑来说自己得了癌症
Then why not keep yourself clean from now. Not only that why not work for sahaja yoga
那为何不现在就让自己洁净 不只如此,为何不为霎哈嘉瑜伽工作
for which we are in the kingdom of God.
好让我们活在神的国度
Tomorrow when such people are chosen from this world
将来在世上选取人们进入上帝的国度时
who belong to God’s kingdom then you shall be the chosen ones.
你们就会是被拣选的那群人
Why not do such acts. We are just wasting our time,
为何不这样做? 我们就只是浪费时间
meeting friends, having food with relations, criticizing others.
跟朋友见面,与亲戚共餐,批评他人
Let’s leave all that and improve our ways.
让我们远离那些,并改进我们的方法
We should lead such a life that we are remembered for that.
我们应当引领一种会让自己被别人 记起的生活方式
Lets think like that.
我们要那样想
Nobody should think that he is left with very few years in life and it is difficult to achieve it now.
没有人应该想着,自己没剩多少年 现在要达到那境界会很难
You shall not die.
你们不会死
When you die you are then reborn and this goes on.
当你们死后又会重生,不断持续下去
The why not come out of this cycle(of births and deaths)
那么为何不在一年内脱离这循环 (出生与死亡)
in a year’s time and if you wish you can do that in a week’s time.
如果你们有意愿,甚至可以在一周内达到
You only have to decide once, just once.
你们只需要一次下定决心,只要一次
You can be immensely benefitted by sahaja yoga just by deciding once like this.
像这般地下定决心,你们便能得到 霎哈嘉瑜伽极大的好处
You should be surrendered completely.
你们必须完全地顺服
It is not necessary that you touch my feet but should be surrendered to me from your heart.
不需要碰触我的双足,但要在心中 顺服于我
Some people touch my feet but are not surrendered in their heart.
有些人触碰我的双足却没在心里顺服
One has to be completely surrendered to Me from within.
一个人必须从内在完全顺服
If you are completely surrendered from within then your kundalini remains established on your Atma-Tatva,
如果你们是由衷地内在顺服,那么灵量 会持续在真我原理上建立
just like the flame of a lamp, without any flickering.
就像油灯上的火焰,没有任何闪烁
But one must remain surrendered for that.
但必须一直为此保持顺服
In the surrendered state one experiences Joy, Bliss and God realisation.
在完全顺服的境界,人们会体验到喜悦、 极乐与神的觉醒
Sahaja Yoga is a unparalleled, unique & special thing. Please try to understand this and be involved in it.
霎哈嘉瑜伽是无与伦比的、独特的,特殊的 事物,请试着理解这点并投入其中
The more you identify yourself with Tadatma(oneness with the Divine) state, the more your Atma-tatva shines.
你们越是让自己认同Tadatma(与神合一)的境界 你们的真我原理便越是闪亮
Nothing is important at all, except that you yourself become the Light.
除了你们让自己成为光,其他事情都不重要
Those who are indulging in nonsense activities all the time are suggested to leave such things.
那些沉溺在各种荒谬的活动的人 建议他们要远离
Those things are not for them. I am telling you one last time.
那些东西不是为他们准备的.我再告诉你们 最后一次
Please take note of it and act on it intelligently.
请把它记下来并明智地去行动
Within us lie many evil tendencies, and within us lie many negativities.
我们内在有着各种邪恶的倾向 有着许多负面
These influence us to do evil deeds.
这会影响我们去做出邪恶的行为
To act under their influence is like becoming Satana yourself.
在它们的影响下去做事情,就像是 把自己变成撒旦
Now it is upto you to either become a Satan or become God.
现在要成为撒旦还是成为神 取决于你们自己
Now if you wish to become Satan then it is a different thing and I am not your Guru for that.
如果现在你们想变成撒旦,那又不一样 我不是这方面的导师
But if you wish to become God then I am your Guru.
但如果你们想变成神,那么我是你们的导师
But you should save yourself from becoming Satan.
但你们必须拯救自己,不去成为撒旦
First thing to note is that on the night of new-moon and full-moon,
首先要记下的是,在新月与满月的日子
always there are dangers on your left and right sides.
你们的左右脉会遇到危险
Specially on these two days, that is, the nights of new moon and full moon, you should sleep very early at night.
特别是这两天,新月与满月的日子 晚上必须很早睡
After singing bhajans, bow down before the photograph, meditate,
唱完拜赞歌后,对着照片叩拜、静坐
and keep your  attention on Sahasrara and go to sleep after taking bandhan.
把注意力放顶轮,划班单后去睡觉
That means you go into the unconscious the moment your attention is at your Sahasrara.
这意味着当你们注意力在顶轮时 你们便进入无意识的境界
There, give yourself a bandhan and you are saved.
在那儿给自己划班单,然后你们会被拯救
During these two nights it should be observed particularly.
在这两晚应该要特别留意一下
The night of new moon, you should meditate especially on Shri Shiva.
在新月之夜,你们应该特别对湿婆神冥想
You should sleep after meditating on Shri Shiva
你们应该在对湿婆神冥想后睡觉
– that is the Spirit – and completely surrender yourself to Him.
他是灵,你要完全地对祂顺服
On the night of full moon, you should meditate on Shri Rama and surrender yourself to Him for protection.
在满月之夜你们应该对罗摩冥想
The meaning of the word Ramchandra is  “creativity”.
"Ramchandra"的意思是创造力
You should completely dedicate your creative powers to Him.
你们应该完全地将自己的创造力奉献给祂
Thus you have to take special care of yourself on these two days.
所以在这两天你们要特别地照顾好自己
However on the seventh and ninth days of Lunar fortnights (according to the Indian Calendar “saptami” and “navami”)
但在阴历两星期(根据印度月历,saptami与navami 两周)中的第七与第九天
you have my special blessings.
你们会获得特别的祝福
Remember that you are specially blessed by Me  on these two days.
记住在这两天你们会获得我特别的祝福
Make some special arrangements so that you can have proper meditation on these days.
特别安排一下,好使你们能在这些天进行 合适的静坐
You must do collective meditation only at those places which have been purified by my Feet(where I have physically visited).
你们应当只在那些经我双足净化过 (我亲身走过)的场地集体静坐
You should not be doing collective meditation at your home by inviting someone.
你们不应当在家邀请别人进行集体静坐
Even with your relations also you should not be doing collective meditation.
即便是你们的亲戚也不该和你进行集体静坐
You should be doing collective meditation only wherever I have told you to do so.
你们只该在我跟你们说过的地方集体静坐
You should also be discussing about sahaja yoga for a very long time at such a place where I have not put My Feet.
在我未曾放过双足的地方,你们也不该长时间的 讨论霎哈嘉瑜伽
Because at such places, bhoots shall start talking thru yourself and you shall start fighting among your self.
因为在这样的地方,亡灵会开始透过你们说话 而你们之间会开始起争执
I am saying this because even now you are not free from the clutches of Bhoots.
我会这样说是因为,即便现在 你们也未曾摆脱亡灵的束缚
You are not able to know when the bhoot enters into your being and takes over.
亡灵进入身体并接管时你们还无法察觉到
This is how you should protect yourself. And whenever you are going out, leaving your home, give yourself a bandhan; always be in the bandhan.
你们该这么保护自己.每当你们出门去,离开家 给自己划班单,总是让自己处在班单的保护中
If you come across someone having a catch on Agnya, give him a bandhan, even with your attention it can be done.
如果你遇到个额轮堵塞的人,给他个班单 即使用注意力也能做到
Never argue with a person who’s caught on Agnya; it is a foolishness to do so.
绝不与额轮堵塞的人争辩,这么做是很愚蠢的
Can you ever argue with a person who is caught on Agnya, who is a bhoot ?
你们能够和一个额轮堵塞的人、 一个亡灵争辩吗
Do not argue with a person who is caught on Agnya. ‘Never’. Just agree with him for whatever he says.
不要和额轮堵塞的人争辩,绝不! 无论他说什么都同意
Go on saying yes,yes, you are right.
持续说"是的,是的,你是对的"
Because whenever we have a mentally challenged person we only say yes, yes whatever you are saying it right.
因为每当我们遇到好思维辩论的人,就只要说 "是的,是的,无论你说了甚么都对"
Never argue with a person who is caught on agnya.
绝不和额轮堵塞的人争辩
You should also not be arguing with a person who is caught on vishuddhi.
你们也不该和喉轮有堵塞的人争辩
And never go near a  person who is caught on Sahasrara!
千万别接近顶轮堵塞的人
Have no contact with him. Tell him to improve his Sahasrara first.
不要和他联系.告诉他先改善顶轮
You should not be hesitant in telling him, “Your Sahasrara is caught. Put it right.”
你们应该毫不犹豫地跟他说: "你的顶轮堵塞了,纠正它"
Sahasrara should be kept clean.
应该保持顶轮洁净
If anyone has started catching on Sahasrara, then he should immediately take help from other Sahaja Yogis,
如果任何人的顶轮开始感染,他应该马上 从其他霎哈嘉瑜伽士那儿获得帮助
“Do something and clear my Sahasrara”. If someone who is caught on Sahasrara talks to you, you should tell him, ‘you are my enemy’.
"做些事情,清洁我的顶轮". 如果任何顶轮感染的人 跟你们说话,你们该跟他说:"你是我的敌人"
Never talk to him as long as he is caught on sahasrara.
只要他顶轮感染就一直不要跟他说话
As regards a person caught on Heart, you should help that person, as far as possible.
至于心轮受感染的人,你们应该尽可能地 伸出援手
Put bandhan on his heart, put your hand on your heart
对他的心划班单,将你的手放在你的心
and take him to the photograph of Shri Mataji. You must take care of heart chakra.
将他带到Shri Mataji的相片前 你们必须看顾心轮
May be, sometimes one may get a problem on the heart chakra.
也许有时一个人可能会发生心轮的问题
You must help others clear the heart chakra.
你们必须要帮助他人清洁心轮
But many people have no heart ! They are very dry personalities.
但许多人却没有心.他们是很枯燥的人
And you cannot do anything for such dry persons, even if you wish to.
你们无法为这样的人做些什么,即便你们想
So you should leave them alone. However, if they come to you and ask for your help then advise them to first leave Hatha Yoga,
所以你们应该不管他们.但如果他们来向你们 寻求帮助,那么建议他们首先要离开哈达瑜伽
and then ask them to leave other unimportant things in life. They should be asked to learn to love others
然后要求他们放下人生中的其他不重要的事情 他们应该被要求去爱其他人
and if they cannot love human beings then they should at least start loving dogs,cats.
如果他们无法爱人类,那么他们至少应该 先开始学会爱猫狗
Love everyone. Love children. Never aggress on to children. In fact one should never aggress on anyone.
爱每个人、爱孩子,事实上没有人 应该侵犯任何人
Never hurt anyone.
绝不要伤害他人
Nobody should beat the children. No sahaja yogi should ever beat your children with your hands.
不应该打孩子.任何霎哈嘉瑜伽士都 不应该用手打孩子
Never beat others with your hands, never.  Never get angry with anyone.
不要用手打人,绝不.绝不要对任何人生气
Particularly, Sahaja Yogis should never get angry. Without getting annoyed, they should improve everything tactfully and intelligently.
尤其霎哈嘉瑜伽士不应该生气.他们应当不发怒 能圆滑地、聪明地改进一切
Never get angry.
绝不要生气
You must pray for, How should the day to day life of a sahaja yogi be. One should think about it.
你们必须要祈求,(让我学会)霎哈嘉瑜伽士的 日常生活举止.你们应该好好想想
I have told you in many ways. Similarly this organisation that we have of ‘Anant Jeevan’(Eternal Life),
我已经用各种方式告诉过你们.类似地,我们拥有的 这个"Anant Jeevan(生命永恒)"的组织
for which eight to ten people should come together and think what is to be done.
八到十个人应该聚在一起,思考该为它做些什么
You must all contribute to it and should give their services for it.
你们必须对此有贡献,应为此服务
All those who still haven’t given their names should give them to Mr Pradhan,
所有还没给名字的,都应该把名字 给Pradhan先生
and we are going to start a quarterly publication in which all my letters, messages, lectures will be printed
而我们会开始发行季刊,里头会印制我的信、 讯息、演讲等
and apart from that if you have any experiences to be shared then do it so that these can also be printed in it.
除此之外,如果你们有任何的经验要分享 写出来后也能在这里刊出
Whatever experiences we get from all over India, some of them would be printed in that.
任何我们在整个印度范围内的经历 有些会被印在刊物里
Therefore if you have any experiences keep writing to them.
因此如果你们有什么经历,持续写给他们
Apart from that if you can write an article on sahaja yoga please write and send it for printing.
此外如果你们可以写写关于霎哈嘉瑜伽 的文章,请写下来并发送过来印刷
This way there shall be a quarterly in which there will be some articles in Hindi,
这样每个季度能出版一次 里头会有些文章是印地语
some in Marathi, some in English, and some in Gujarati.
有些是马拉地语,有些是英语,还有些是 古吉拉特语
So we shall be starting printing either together in all these languages or one by one.
我们该开始印制这些,要么全部语言一起 要么分开印制
Everything happens slowly in sahaja yoga.
每件事在霎哈嘉瑜伽里会慢慢地开展
For that you must contribute, give your subscription and take advantage out of it.
为此你们必须要有贡献,订阅 并从中获得益处
If you have any questions
如果你们对此有问题
on this then raise them and I shall answer all of them together.
可以提出来,我会一起回答
We are first starting a quarterly which later be a monthly and then weekly and finally daily,
我们刚开始会发行季刊,稍后会是月刊 然后是周刊,最后是每日发行
but for now it shall be a quarterly publication.
但目前应该是季刊
If you have questions, any problems
如果你们有任何问题、任何麻烦
then please send a letter in my name to Mr Pradhan.
请把信写上我的名字,寄给Pradhan先生
Please don’t write many letters to me as I do not have time.
请不要写太多信给我,我没那么多时间
After that do not say Mother has written to him and not to me.
也不要说"母亲写信给他了却没写给我"
Do not talk in such foolish ways. Sahaja Yoga is not for such people.
不要用这种愚蠢的方式说话 霎哈嘉瑜伽不是给这类人的
You know that your Mother loves you all equally.
你知道你们的母亲无分别地爱每一个人
For some reasons I may not write to some people.
因为一些原因也许我不会给某些人写信
Sometimes She writes to you and sometimes not.
有时她写给你们有时没有
Sometimes I write to those whom I know will never mind if I don’t write to them.
那些并不在意我是否写信给他们的人 有时我会写给他们
And now I am not going to care about those who feel bad if I don’t write to them.
那些如果我没写信给他们就感到难过的人 我现在不会再关心他们
I have cared enough for such people and the result is that those evil people
我已经对这类人关心够多,但结果却是 那些邪恶的人
have remained that way and never improved and we have been troubled.
依然故我,从不改进,导致我们陷入麻烦
All those with whom I have been patient thinking that one they shall improve have not shown any progress
所有那些我曾耐心以对,觉得他们该进步的 却未曾展示过任何进步
and have remained wicked, they have not transformed even wee bit and we have got the pain.
持续冥顽不灵的人,他们甚至一丁点 也没被转化,而我们却受到伤害
Because I had decided that no human being shall be destroyed in this kaliyuga.
因为我曾决定,没有任何人类应该在 这"转换期(Kali Yuga)"被毁灭
I shall not torture any human being. I have given him complete freedom to go either to hell or towards God.
我不该折磨任何人类,我给了他 全然的自由,通往地狱或通往神
I have given you complete freedom.
我给了你们完全的自由
If someone wants to go to hell then I say take faster steps towards it,
如果有人想去地狱,那么我会说 加快脚步去吧
so that I am free from you.
这样我就不用管你了
That arrangement also I have done.
我也会做这样的安排
If you wish to go to hell then I have made arrangements for that also
如果你们想去地狱,那么我也已经安排好
but if you wish to go at the Feet of God, that also is arranged for you.
但如果你们想到达神的莲足 这也能为你们安排好
So I am telling all those who have troubled me, disturbed me
所以我要对那些麻烦我、干扰我、 纠缠我的人说
or tormented me that I have had enough patience
我已经用尽了耐心
and now if anyone troubles me or disturbs me then I have to say very clearly to such persons
现在任何人要是麻烦我或骚扰我 那么我会很清楚的对他说
that now we have no relation with you and that you should leave sahaja yoga.
“我们跟你没有关联,你必须离开霎哈嘉瑜伽"
Such elements, while going out of sahaja yoga show their true colors and disturb us again.
这样的人离开霎哈嘉瑜伽时会露出真面目 再度地骚扰我们
Their true nature is exposed. But I have to tell you that you think about your well being.
他们会显露出真实的本性.但我告诉你们 想想你们的福祉
There is no need to follow them and go to hell.
没有必要跟随他们去地狱
Think about your own well being. There is no need to argue with anyone.
想想你们自己的福祉,没有必要 跟任何人争辩
They shall remain as they were earlier.
他们会跟早先一样
They are very difficult to get transformed.
他们很难被转化
Because they are evil.
因为他们是邪恶的
Those who are good, they may initially behave like them but get transformed very easily.
那些良善的人,可能刚开始会像他们一样 举止,但却会很容易就被转化
Those who are evil are impossible to get transformed
那些邪恶的人则无法被转化
and I have understood this. I have tried enough but such people shall remain as they were.
我已经了解这点了.我尝试够了 这类人会依然故我
You can never transform them.
你无法转化他们
They shall never have wisdom.
他们永远不会有智慧
That’s why there is no need to argue with such people.
因此没有必要去和这类人争论
I have to request you,
我必须要求你们
not to have any kind of relationship with such people.
我要求你们不要跟这类人有任何关联
Slowly they shall be out of sahaja yoga.
他们会慢慢淡出霎哈嘉瑜伽
They are here because they want to destroy whatever you have accomplished.
他们之所以在这里,是因为他们想要 毁灭你们已经达成的一切
You should save yourself from such people. Get your vibrations.
你们应该从这些人手中拯救自己 获得自己的能量
There was a person who wanted to give us a house.
曾经有个人想要(卖)给我们一栋房子
This gentleman came to me and took Realization.
这位先生来到我跟前获得了自觉
But after Realization, he got someone.
但自觉之后,有个人来找他
The visitor said that in Shri Mataji group are just delinquents.
这位访客说,跟随Shri Mataji的人 只是些不正常的人
He received his Realization, he felt vibrations and despite this, believed the visitor.
他获得了自觉,感受到了能量.尽管如此 他还是相信了那位访客
He said then: "I can not give you my house because some things were said ..."
然后他说:"我不能把我的房子给你.因为 有传闻说..."
I replied: "All right, give this gentleman the house" Poor fellow!
我回答说:"好吧,把你的房子给那位先生吧" 可怜的家伙
Nobody wants to buy the house now and he loses, called me daily: "Please buy my house. I'm sorry, forgive me."
现在没人想买他的房子.他受到损失,每天打电话 给我:"请买下我的房子吧.我很抱歉,原谅我"
I repeated: "Did you than to sell this gentleman the house. You are free to do so. "
我重申:"你不是想卖给那位先生吗? 你可以卖给他"
Now he complains, complains: "Shri Mataji's mad at me."
现在他就抱怨, 抱怨"Shri Mataji疯狂对我"
I'm not mad at all, I said: "Sell your house person who told you all these things."
我可一点没疯,我说的是: "谁跟你说的那些事情,把你房子卖给他"
So all those who think they are very intelligent, if they want to go to hell
所有那些自认为十分聪明的人 如果他们想下地狱
I can issue them ticket to hell. It is all under my control.
我可以给他们发放通往地狱的车票 这全都在我控制之下
All those desirous of going to hell can have the ticket from me and I am willing to give it.
那些想要去地狱的,可以从我这里拿到 通往地狱的票,我很乐意发出
Those who want to go the kingdom of God their ticket also I can issue.
那些想要到达神的国度的,我也能 给票给他们
A ticket clerk can issue ticket for any destination
售票员可以签发通往任何目的地的票
but ticket clerk will inform you that if you go this way there will be derailment
但售票员会通知你们,如果走这条路将会脱轨
and immediately on reaching there your  .... will break,
一旦你们到达那儿,……会坏掉
there is no return from there, you cannot come back from there. Return ticket is not available from there.
无路可返,你们无法从那儿再回来了 没有从那出发的回程票
That’s why I am informing you but I do not have to say much about hell, as you know all about it.
这是为何我要告诉你们,但我不会说太多关于 地狱的事,因为你们是知道的
I have told you all this so that you can keep your own instrument clean.
我告诉你们这些,是为了让你们维持 自己工具的洁净
And always keep your sight on higher level. You should not keep your sight low but on higher level.
总是将自己的眼光放的更高.你们不该 让自己眼界过低,要放高些
You have to rise higher. Never look down. You have to rise higher.
你们必须向上提升,绝不要往下看 你们必须向上提升
I am with you at every step, at every place. Everywhere.
我和你们同在,每一步伐、每一居所、 每一处
Wherever You are, at whichever  place you are, I am with you, completely, in person,
无论你们去了哪儿、身处何方,藉由我的灵、 我的话语,我完全地与你们同在
by my spirit and by my word completely.
全然的、亲身的
This is my promise to you.
这是我对你们的承诺
But those who wish to go to Hell, they will also be sucked down.
但对那些想去地狱的,他们也会被往下吸入
That is also arranged.
这也是有安排的
Therefore be careful. Take to higher life.
因此要小心,要选择更高层次的生命
Now I am going to London
现在我要去伦敦
and when I come back I want to see that each one of you should have given realisation to at least ten persons.
当我回来时我想看到,你们每个人至少 都给了十个人自觉
Call others, talk to them about sahaja yoga openly. Don’t feel shy.
把其他人叫来,公开的跟他们讨论 霎哈嘉瑜伽,不要害羞
Tell them about sahaja yoga
告诉他们霎哈嘉瑜伽
how truthful it is. It is the religion of Truth. It is for real.
是多么富有真理.这是真理的宗教 这是真实的
Gather people,
把人们聚集在一起
talk to them wherever you find them.
与他们交谈,无论在哪儿都可以
Everyone of you should take the photograph and each one should give photo in ten homes.
你们每个人都要拿着照片,每个人要 给十户人家发照片
It is a very good way that each person contributes to take ten photographs.
每个人拿十张照片,这是个很好的方法
Give these photos to ten such homes where there will be respect towards the photo,
照片发给十户会尊重、会崇拜这照片
where it will be worshipped and where sahaja yoga can be accepted.
并且能接受霎哈嘉瑜伽的人家
By this way only we can spread sahaja yoga.
只有这样我们才能传播霎哈嘉瑜伽
We do not want to have much publicity because
我们不想要大量的宣传
whenever we do publicity then dirty people are also attracted and the good people do not come.
因为每当我们大量宣传,污秽的人 也会被吸引来,而好人却不来
Therefore it is better to serve sahaja yoga all the time
因此最好是总是给霎哈嘉瑜伽服务
and make yourself wealthy(spiritually) by it.
让自己因此(灵性上)富裕
May God Bless you.
愿神祝福你们
My complete blessings are with you. My heart, mind,
我完全的祝福与你们同在.我的心、思维、
body be always engaged in your service.
身体都忙着为你们工作
I am not away from you even for a moment.
我一刻都未曾离开你们
Whenever you will remember me anywhere
无论任何地方,每当你们想起我
by just closing your eyes , at that moment I shall come to you with all my powers, ‘
你们只要闭上眼,在那一刻我会 带着全部的力量与你们同在
‘Shankh,Chakra, Gada, Padma Garud  layee siddhari’ ( Just as Lord Krishana came riding on his Condour from Dwarika, with all his Divine weapons – Shankh, Chakra, Gada, Padma when Draupadi called Him – I shall be before you in no time)
"Shankh,Chakra,Gada,Padma Garud layee siddhari" (就像当杜鲁柏迪叫唤我主克里希纳时,祂骑着Condour 带着祂所有的武器,从Dwarika赶来一般 我会马上在你们面前出现)
Even for a moment I shall not be late
一刻也不会延误
ut you will have to be Mine.
但你们必须是属于我的
This is very important.
这很重要
If you are Mine then I shall not be late even for a moment.
如果你们是属于我的,我一刻也不会延误
I shall be before you.
我会出现在你们面前
Let God bless you all and give you wisdom.
让神祝福你们所有人并赐予你们智慧